Guide to the Frederick Emmons Terman Papers SC0160
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Harvard Radio Research Laboratory, 1942-1946; Series I
  - PROJECT COMMITTEE: PAPERS ASSOCIATED WITH MEETINGS
    - #27 - 32 (Feb. - March 1944) (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - #33 - 42 (March - June 1944) (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - #43 - 52 (June - August 1944) (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - #53 - 64 (Sept. - Oct. 1944) (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - #65 - 73 (Nov. - Dec. 1944) (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - #74 - 79 (Jan. - Feb. 1945) (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - #80 - 84 (Feb. - March 1945) (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - #85 - 89 (March - April 1945) (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - #90 - 92 (May 1945) (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - #93 - 95 (May - June 1945) (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - #96 - 98 (June - July 1945) (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - #99 - 101 (July 1945) (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - #102 - 105 (July - Aug. 1945) (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Minutes: Summary of business at meetings 1 61; Minutes #1 - 24 (May 1943 - Jan. 1944) (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Minutes: #25 - 50 (Jan. 1944 - July 1944) (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Minutes: #51 - 73 (Aug. 1944 - Jan. 1945) (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Minutes: #84 - 95 (March - June 1945) (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Minutes: #74 - 83 (Jan. - March 1945) (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Minutes: #95 - 105 (June - Aug. 1945) (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Executive Committee: Papers associated with meetings. #1 - 18, Oct. 1943 - July 1944. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Executive Committee: Minutes #1-- 17, Oct. 1943 - Oct. 1944. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Management Committee: Papers associated with meetings. Aug. - Nov. 1945. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Management Committee: Minutes Aug. - Nov. 1945. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - PUBLICITY
    - Magazine and Radio Publicity. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper Clippings: 1944-46. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Press Parties; News Releases. 1945. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Radar Magazine. 1944-45. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Photographs: American-British Laboratory. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Photographs: Navy Installations of R.C.M. Equipment. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Photographs: Press Photos. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Photographs: War in the Ether: Operational Radar Countermeasures in WW II (Photos from report of that name. Numbers on back of photos indicate section of report they were to be inserted into.) (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Photographs: "window." (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - ADMINISTRATIVE HISTORIES AND OPERATIONAL REPORTS
    - Administrative History of the Radio Research Laboratory by F. E. Terman, Director. March 21, 1946. Bound. 64 numbered pages, 80 pages of figures, 11 pages of Appendix A. (Note: Although report's author is officially listed as F. E. Terman, Dr. Terman says that report was actually written by Oswald G. Villard, Jr.) (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Administrative Report of the American-British Laboratory of Division 15 of the NDRC. October 1, 1945. Bound, 84 pages. Illustrated with photographs and charts. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Electronics Warfare: A report on Radar Countermeasures. Released by the Joint Board on Scientific Information Policy for: OSRD, War Department, Navy Department. 1945. Pamphlet, 38 pp. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - "Flack Radar Countermeasures in the European Theater of Operations: A Review and Evaluation of their Use by the 8th Air Force." [n.d.] Mimeographed, 30 pp. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - "Intelligence Information on R.C.M. effectiveness in the E.T.O." Prepared by R.S. O'Brien and R.A. Soderman. June 16, 1945. Mimeographed. 56 numbered pages, 4 appendices. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - The Operational Use of RCM in the ETO as related to the Technical History of the American-British Laboratory. NDRC Division of Radio Coordination. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - "Philosophy, History, and Operation of the Radio Research Laboratory Transition Department." By E. D. Brooks, Jr. Nov. 1, 1945. Typescript in binder. 44 typed, numbered pages; 44 unnumbered pages of appendices. (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - "Radar: A Report on Science of War." Released by the Joint Board on Scientific Information Policy for: OSRD; War Department; Navy Department. 1945. Pamphlet, 51 pages. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - War in the Ether: Operational Radar Countermeasures in World War II. Mimeographed, in two parts. Part 1 - "European Theater of Operations," 101 pages. Part 2 - "RCM in the Pacific Theaters of Operation," 132 pages. [n.d.] (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Radar Countermeasures, RCM: A Brief Look at the NDRC Division 15's Impact on Radio Countermeasures (RCM) Activities During the Second World War. Association of Old Crows History Committee, Armand J. Morin, editor. [1982] (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - List of Sources of Information on RCM in World War II. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - R.R.L. REPORTS
    - R.R.L. Reports checked out to persons outside Lab. 1953-58. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - List of R.R.L. Documents; Classification of Documents. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Index of code words and abbreviations. Jan. 29, 1943. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Special Reports: 1, 3, 4. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Special Reports: 6, 7, 7a, 9. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Special Reports: 11, 13, 14, 15, 15a. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Special Reports: 16, 17, 18, 20. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Special Reports: 21, 22, 23. (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Special Reports: 24, 26, 28, 30. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Special Reports: 31, 32, 34, 35. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Special Reports: 36 40. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Special Reports: 41, 42, 44. (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Special Reports: 45, 46, 48, 49, 50. (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Special Reports: 51 54. (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Special Reports: 57 60. (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Special Reports: 61, 62, 64, 64a, 64b. (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Special Reports: 66 - 68, 70, 70a. (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Special Reports: 72 - 74. (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Special Reports: 76 - 79. (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Special Reports: 81 - 84. (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Special Reports: 86, 86a, 88, 89, 90. (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Special Reports: 91, 92, 94, 95. (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Special Reports: 96 - 99. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Special Reports: 100. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Special Reports: 100a. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Special Reports: 101 - 103. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Special Reports: 105, 106, 107, 109, 110. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Special Reports: 111 - 114. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Special Reports: 115 - 119. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Special Reports: 121 - 125. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Special Reports: 126 - 130. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Special Reports: 131 - 134. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Special Reports: 135 - 138, 140. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Special Reports: 141 - 144. (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Special Reports: 146 - 150. (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Special Reports: 151 - 155. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Special Reports: 156 - 160. (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Special Reports: 161 - 165. (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Special Reports: 166 - 170. (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Special Reports: 171 - 175. (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Special Reports: 177 - 180. (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Special Reports: 181, 183 - 186. (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Special Reports: 187, 187a, 188, 190. (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Special Reports: 191, 192, 194, 195. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Special Reports: 196 - 200. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Special Reports: 201, 202, 203, 203a, 205. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Special Reports: 206 - 210. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Special Reports: 211 - 215. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Special Reports: 216 - 220. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Special Reports: 221 - 224. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Special Reports: 225 - 230. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Special Reports: 231 - 235. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Special Reports: 236 - 240. (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Special Reports: 241 - 244. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Special Reports: 245 - 247. (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Special Reports: 251 - 255. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Special Reports: 256 - 260. (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Special Reports: 262 - 264. (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Special Reports: 265, 266, 268, 270. (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Special Reports: 272, 274, 276, 277 280. (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Special Reports: 281 - 285. (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Special Reports: 286, 287, 289, 290. (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Special Reports: 291 - 295. (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Special Reports: 296 - 298. (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Equipment Specifications Reports: 8, 11, 12, 13, 13a, 13b. (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Equipment Specifications Reports: 14 - 17, 19, 20. (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Equipment Specifications Reports: 22, 24 - 28. (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Test Reports: 1 - 5. (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Test Reports: 6 - 10. (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Test Reports: 11 - 18; 20. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Test Reports: 21 - 26. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Test Reports: 27 - 30. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Test Reports: 32 - 35. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Test Reports: 36 - 40. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Test Reports: 41 - 45. (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Test Reports: 46 - 50. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Test Reports: 51 - 56; 59, 60. (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Memorandum Test Reports: MTR 1 MTR 10. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Memorandum Test Reports: MTR 11 MTR 21. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Technical Memoranda: 1 - 9. (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Technical Memoranda: 10 - 20. (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Technical Memoranda: 21 - 28. (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Technical Memoranda: 36, 38, 38a, 39, 40, 40a. (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Technical Memoranda: 30 - 35. (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Technical Memoranda: 41 - 47. (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Technical Memoranda: 48 - 54. (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Technical Memoranda: 55 - 59. (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Technical Memoranda: 61 - 66. (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Technical Memoranda: 81 - 85, 87. (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Technical Memoranda: 67 - 69;, 71; 73 - 80. (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Technical Memoranda: 88 - 94. (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Technical Memoranda: 95 - 101. (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Technical Memoranda: 102 - 108. (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Technical Memoranda: 109 - 113; 115 - 117; 119. (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Technical Memoranda: 120 - 126. (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Technical Memoranda: 127 - 129; 131 - 135. (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Technical Memoranda: 136 - 141. (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - RRL Internal Reports: Group A. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - RRL Internal Reports: Group B. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - RRL Internal Reports: Group D. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - RRL Internal Reports: Group E. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - RRL Internal Reports: Group F. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - RRL Internal Reports: Group J. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - RRL Internal Reports: Group M. (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - RRL Internal Reports: X Series. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - RRL Internal Reports: All other groups. (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Progress Reports: 5, 8, 10, 12, 19, 27, 33, 43, 47, (Oct. 1942 - June 1943). (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Internal Progress Reports: 13 - 15 (Oct. - Dec. 1943). (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Internal Progress Reports: 16 - 18 (Jan. - March 1944). (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Internal Progress Reports: 19, 20 (April - May 1944). (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Internal Progress Reports: 21 - 22 (June - July 1944). (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Internal Progress Reports: 23 - 24 (Aug. - Sept. 1944). (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Internal Progress Reports: 25 - 26 (Nov. 1944 - Jan. 1945). (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Internal Progress Reports: 27 - 28 (Jan. - May 1945). (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Internal Progress Reports: 29 (May - July 1945). (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Instruction Books: 1; 8a - 8d. (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Instruction Books: 9 12. (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Instruction Books: 13 - 17. (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Instruction Books: 18 - 19. (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Instruction Books: 20 - 25. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Instruction Books: 26; 28 - 30. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Instruction Books: 31; 33 -37. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Instruction Books: 38 - 39. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Instruction Books: 40 - 45. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Instruction Books: 46 - 50. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Instruction Books: 51 (large binder). (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Instruction Books: 54 - 56; 58 - 59. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Instruction Books: 61, 62) 65, 68. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Instruction Books: 70 - 74. (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Instruction Books: 75 - 78. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Instruction Books: 80, 81, 83, 85, 86, 88, 89. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Instruction Books: 90, 91, 93. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Technical SEMINARS: Lectures 1 8; 12 - 14. (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Liaison Reports: Daniell. 10 34 (July 1944 - Jan. 1945). (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Liaison Reports: Daniell. 35 49 (Feb. - Sept. 1945). (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Liaison Reports: Hammett. 1 - 4 (Feb. - March 1945). (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Liaison Reports: Holt. 1- 17 (June 1944 - Aug. 1945). (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Liaison Reports: Villard. 1 - 15 (Feb. 1944 - Aug. 1945). (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Liaison Reports: Miscellaneous. 1945. (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Teletype Conferences: European Theater of Operations. June - July 1944. (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Teletype Conferences: E.T.O. July - Oct. 1944. (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Teletype Conferences: E.T.O. Nov. 1944 - Jan. 1945. (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Teletype Conferences: E.T.O. Jan. - May 1945. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Teletype Conferences: Mediterranean Theater of Operations July - Dec. 1944. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Teletype Conferences: M.T.O. Jan. - May 1945. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Teletype Conferences: Pacific operations March - June 1945. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Teletype Conferences: Pacific Operations: June - Aug. 1945. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Chaff and rope samples. Note: Dr. Terman says that the aluminum and paper squares in the net bag were not produced by the Harvard R.R.L., though they were a type of radar countermeasure. (Box 17)
- Stanford School of Engineering, 1925-1946; Series II
  Frederick Terman participated in the activates of the Stanford School of Engineering at all levels, first as a student, and later in-teaching appointments ranging from Instructor in Communication to Dean of the School. The papers in Series II document his entire range of professional service to the School. For further information on the history of the Engineering School at Stanford, see Stanford University Archives collection SC 165, Engineering School Records.
  Boxes 1 -4: Electrical Engineering Correspondence, 1931-46. Alphabetically arranged subject files of correspondence and memoranda related to Dr. Terman's career as a faculty member, and from 1937 to 1945, Executive Head of the Department of Engineering.
  Boxes 6 -9: Student-faculty research, 1928-35. Laboratory notes, reports, graphs, articles and correspondence related to research projects undertaken in the Electronic Laboratory under the direction of Dr. Terman. Some of these projects were collaborative efforts between Terman and his students, while others were entirely student work. Each folder contains the papers pertaining to a specific research project, and the folders are filed chronologically.
  Boxes 10 -12: I.T.T. invention disclosures, 1936-42. Research notes, reports, and correspondence related to an agreement with the International Telephone and Telegraph Company. I.T.T. supported the Communication Laboratory in two ways, First, it provided grants to underwrite the cost of certain specific research projects that interested the company. Further, it made an annual lump sum payment to support basic research in the laboratory. In return, I.T.T. was given "first refusal" rights on any inventions which were discovered in the course of this research. The general research problems were usually suggested by Dr. Terman, and worked on by graduate students as assignments of theses. If any promising ideas arose, they were submitted to I.T.T. as invention disclosures, and the company determined whether it wished to negotiate for patents. Although no major inventions resulted from this arrangement, it was very beneficial to Stanford, providing needed support to the Communication Laboratory in a significant stage of its development. This group of papers shows an early stage of the University-industry cooperation that Dr. Terman actively fostered.
  Boxes 13 -17: Stanford Electronic Laboratories Correspondence, 1951-5 As Dean of Engineering, Dr. Terman was also the director of the Stanford Electronics Laboratories, which consisted of the Electronic Research Laboratory, primarily for unclassified basic research, sponsored research contracts. These boxes contain the administrative files of the laboratories, including general correspondence, contracts, personnel and budget information, arranged alphabetically by subject.
  Box 18: Microwave Laboratory Correspondence, 1949-54. The Microwave Laboratory was administered jointly by the Physics and Electrical Engineering Departments. Edward L. Ginzton was the director of this laboratory, and most of this box actually consists of copies of Dr. Ginzton's administrative correspondence made for Terman's information. The folders are arranged alphabetically by subject.
  Box 19: Teaching materials. This box contains syllabi, lecture notes, and course evaluations for several electric engineering courses taught by Dr. Terman. All of these items are undated except the evaluations, which date from 1952 to 1954.
  - ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING CORRESPONDENCE
    - A. 1937 - 41. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Appointments. 1931 - 36. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Appointments. 1937 - 46. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - B. 1934 - 41. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Bell Telephone Company. 1929 36. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - C. 1934 - 41. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Communications Laboratory, Reports on. 1927 35. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - D. 1932 - 41. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - E. 1935 - 41. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Eastern Trip. 1938. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Employment Information. 1932 36. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Employment Information. 1937 40. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Engineer's Council for Professional Development. 1936 - 40. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - English for Engineers. 1931 - 33. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - F. 1937 - 41. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Former Students. 1931 - 33. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Food Research Institute - soundproofing. 1932. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Former Students. 1934 - 35. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Former Students. 1936. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - G. 1936 - 40. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Geophysics. 1938. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Gifts. 1927 - 33. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Gifts. 1934 - 45. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Gifts - Paul Davis Information. 1937 41. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - H. 1934 - 41. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - I. 1935 - 41. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - J. 1935 - 41. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - K. 1935 - 41. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Klystron Project 1939 - 40. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Klystron Project 1941 - 43. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - L. 1934 - 41. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - M. 1935 - 40. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Morris, Samuel B. 1936 - 41. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - N. 1936 - 40. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - 0. 1935 - 39. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - P. 1934 - 41. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Palo Alto Police Radio. 1933 - 34. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Prospective Students. 1931 - 35. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Q. 1939. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - R. 1935 - 41. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Recommendations. 1934 - 37. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Reports on school and department activities. 1926 - 30. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Research Projects - miscellaneous. 1940 - 46. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Ryan High Voltage Laboratory Dedication. 1940. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Ryan Laboratory: Impulse Generator (Gardner Company). 1938 - 44. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Ryan Laboratory: Impulse Generator (K-P-F Company). 1939 - 44. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - S. 1934 - 41. (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Ryan Laboratory: Impulse Generator (Pacific Electric Corp.). 1939 - 41. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Spangenberg Position - candidates. 1937. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - T. 1937 - 41. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Travel. 1932 - 35. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - V. 1935 - 40. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - W. 1935 - 41. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Wide-Grid Tube Project. 1938 - 39. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Wilbur, Ray Lyman. 1936 - 43. (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - X, Y, Z. 1937 - 39. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - DEAN'S PERSONAL CORRESPONDENCE., 1946-1954
    - A (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - B (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - C (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - D (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - E (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - F (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - G (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - H (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - I (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - J (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - K (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - L (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - M (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Mc (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - N (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - 0 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - P (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - R (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - S (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - T (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - U (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - V (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - W (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - X, Y, Z (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - STUDENT-FACULTY RESEARCH., 1928-1935
    notes, lab reports, graphs, reprints, correspondence about papers, arranged chronologically
    - The Circle Diagram of a Transmission Network. 1926. (Box 6, Folder I)
    - Transient Skin Effect. 1926. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - The Electrical Engineering Research Situation in American Universities. 1927. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Effective Heating of Code Transmitters. 1928. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Screen Grid Tubes. With B. Dysart. 1928. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Inverted Vacuum Tube. 1928. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Audio Frequency Transformers. Marcel Lissman and I. E. Wood. 1929. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - High-Efficiency, High Output Vacuum Tube Oscillator. (Illustrations to accompany thesis by E. H. Fisher). 1929. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Some Properties of Vacuum Tube Detection. 1929. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Harmonic Generation by means of Grid Circuit Distortion. With D. E. Chambers and E. H. Fisher. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Induction Frequency Changer. 1930 - 31. (Box 7, Folder I)
    - Induction Frequency Changer: Data. Philip Ekstrand. 1931 - 32. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Induction Frequency Changer: Notebooks. Philip Ekstrand. 1931 - 32. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Induction Frequency Changer: Summaries of work. Philip Ekstrand. 1931 - 32. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Wunderlich Tube. 1932. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Variable Resonator Research. Philip Ekstrand. 1932 - 33. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Resistance Stabilized Oscillators. With Philip Ekstrand. 1933. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Tuned Class B and Class C amplifiers. M. M. Santour. 1933. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Resonant Transmission Lines as High-Frequency Circuit Elements. 1934. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Low Loss Coils. 1935. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Studies by Frederick Terman. 1928 - 35. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Class C Amplifier Analysis. Contains work by W. C. Roake, M. M. Santour, John Ferns, Philip Ekstrand. 1933 - 36. (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Electron Motion. Victor Carson. 1938. (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Harmonic Generator Research: Data. 1938. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Analysis and Design of Harmonic Generators. 1938. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - A High-Efficiency Grid-Modulated Amplifier. With John Woolyard. 1938. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Condenser Input. Wilton Abbott. 1938. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - The Condenser Input Rectifier. Richard Chard. 1939. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Frequency Response Characteristics of Amplifiers Employing Negative Feedback. With Wen-Yuan Pan. 1939. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Research Notebooks. Chung-Kuei Chang. 1939 - 40. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Detection: Data and papers. Chung-Kuei Chang. 1939 - 40. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - A Theoretical and Experimental Study of Detectors. Chung-Kuei Chang. 1940. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Resistance-coupled Amplifier Studies. With William Hewlett, Charles Palmer, Wen-Yuan Pan. (Box 9, Folder 3)